|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Privacy Policy / Your California Privacy Rights** | [PRINT](javascript:window.print();) \| [CLOSE](javascript:window.close();) |
| **Active Date: September 19, 2022**<br><br>**Previous Revisions: October 27, 2006; February 26, 2008; March 12, 2008; June 26, 2008; July 31, 2009; January 27, 2015; November 18, 2016; March 31, 2017**<br><br>**Privacy Policy / Your California Privacy Rights**<br><br>USA Interactive, Inc. (“Company,” “we” or “us”) reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time simply by posting such revision, so we encourage you to review it periodically. In order to track any changes to this Privacy Policy, we will include a historical reference at the top of this document.<br><br>This Privacy Policy will tell you, among other things:<br><br>* [Your California privacy rights.](#link1)<br>* [How we collect information and what information we collect.](#link2)<br>* [How we may use information.](#link3)<br>* [How we may share information.](#link4)<br>* [Your choices regarding the sharing of information.](#link5)<br><br>Click on any of the above links to go directly to the corresponding section of this Privacy Policy.<br><br>**ACKNOWLEDGEMENT/YOUR AGREEMENT**<br><br>Company websites are not intended for use by individuals under the age of 18 or those who are not legal residents of the United States. By using our website or submitting information to us, you consent to the Company’s use and sharing of the information collected or submitted as described in this Privacy Policy. If you are not 18 years of age or older and a valid resident of the United States or you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, do not provide us with any information or use any of the products or services offered or provided on Company websites or through Company technology.<br><br>### Nevada Privacy Rights<br><br>Under Nevada law, Nevada residents may submit a request directing us not to make certain disclosures of personal information we maintain about them.<br><br>To exercise this right, please [click here](https://www.retailer-savings.com/contact.cgi?config=9597) to contact us.<br><br>### California Privacy Rights<br><br>This section contains disclosures required by the California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA") and applies only to "personal information" that is subject to the CCPA. This privacy policy conforms with [WCAG 2.0 accessibility guidelines](https://www.w3.org/WAI/GL/WCAG20/). To request this privacy policy in an alternate format, please contact us at (866) 436-7542.<br><br>**Personal Information We Collect, Disclose for a Business Purpose, and Sell.** We may collect the following categories of personal information about California consumers identified in the chart below:<br><br>* Personal and online identifiers (such as first and last name, email address, or unique and online identifiers);<br>* Categories of information described in Section 1798.80(e) of the California Civil Code (such as physical characteristics or description, insurance policy number, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information );<br>* Demographics and characteristics such as race; religion; sex/gender; gender identity, gender expression; sexual orientation; marital status; medical condition ; military or veteran status; national origin; ancestry; disability ;<br>* Internet or other electronic network activity information (such as browsing history, search history, interactions with a website, email, application, or advertisement);<br>* Geolocation information; professional or employment-related information; education information;<br>* Inferences drawn from the aforementioned information about your predicted characteristics and preferences; and<br>* Other information about you that is linked to the aforementioned personal information.<br><br>As further set forth below, in the past 12 months, we have disclosed and sold California consumers' personal information to third parties for business or commercial purposes.<br><br>**Categories of Sources.** We collect this personal information from the following categories of sources:<br><br>* Consumers;<br>* Service providers;<br>* Affiliates not under the USA Interactive, Inc. brand;<br>* Consumer data resellers;<br>* Nonprofit organizations; and<br>* Government entities.<br><br>**Why We Collect, Use, and Share California Information.** We use and disclose the personal information we collect for our commercial and business purposes, as further described in this Privacy Policy. These commercial and business purposes include, without limitation:<br><br>* Our commercial purposes, including marketing, advertising, authentication, identity resolution, fraud prevention, cybersecurity or risk fulfillment services, and facilitating transactions.<br>* Our business purposes as identified in the CCPA, which include:<br><br>* Auditing related to our interactions with you;<br>* Legal compliance;<br>* Detecting and protecting against security incidents, fraud, and illegal activity;<br>* Debugging;<br>* Performing services (for us or our service provider) such as account servicing, processing orders and payments, and analytics;<br>* Internal research for technological improvement;<br>* Internal operations;<br>* Activities to maintain and improve our services; and<br>* Other one-time uses.<br><br>**Recipients of California Personal Information.** We sell the categories of personal information designated above to the categories of third parties listed below:<br><br>* Advertising/marketing companies;<br>* Advertising networks;<br>* Internet service providers;<br>* Apparel & accessory companies;<br>* Automotive companies;<br>* Business services/agencies;<br>* Business to business companies;<br>* Parenting product companies;<br>* Communication services companies;<br>* Consumer packaged goods companies;<br>* Health and wellness product and service companies;<br>* Marketing data companies;<br>* Data analytics providers;<br>* Operating systems and platforms;<br>* Social networks;<br>* Consumer data resellers;<br>* Educational institutions & companies;<br>* Electronics companies;<br>* Energy and utility companies;<br>* Financial services companies;<br>* Food & beverage companies;<br>* Gift product companies;<br>* Lifestyle & interest product companies;<br>* Manufacturing companies;<br>* Not for profit organizations;<br>* Publishing product companies;<br>* Technology/computer software companies;<br>* Telecommunications companies;<br>* Travel, leisure, & entertainment companies;<br>* Affiliates not under the USA Interactive, Inc. brand; and<br>* Government entities.<br><br>We disclose the categories of personal information designated above to the categories of third parties listed below for business purposes:<br><br>* Service providers;<br>* Affiliates not under the USA Interactive, Inc. brand;<br>* Government entities;<br>* Advertising/marketing companies;<br>* Advertising networks;<br>* Internet service providers;<br>* Data analytics providers;<br>* Operating systems and platforms;<br>* Social networks; and<br>* Consumer data resellers.<br><br>**Your Rights Regarding Personal Information.** California residents have certain rights with respect to the personal information collected by businesses. If you are a California resident, you may exercise the following rights regarding your personal information, subject to certain exceptions and limitations:<br><br>* For certain categories of personal information, the right to request a list of what personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the names and addresses of those third parties;<br>* The right to know the categories and specific pieces of personal information we collect, use, disclose, and sell about you, the categories of sources from which we collected your personal information, our purposes for collecting or selling your personal information, the categories of your personal information that we have either sold or disclosed for a business purpose, and the categories of third parties with which we have shared personal information;<br>* The right to request that we delete the personal information we have collected from you or maintain about you.<br>* The right to opt out of our sale(s) of your personal information. Please note that if you opt out of certain types of sales, we will be unable to provide you with the services that rely on such sales.<br>* The right not to receive discriminatory treatment for the exercise of the privacy rights conferred by the CCPA.<br>    <br>    To exercise any of the above rights, please contact us using the following information and submit the required verifying information, as further described below:<br>    <br>    * By phone at (866) 436-7542.<br>    <br>    * Online at:<br>    * The following link for requests to know: [click here](https://www.retailer-savings.com/contact2.cgi?config=9597).<br>    * The following link for requests to delete: [click here](https://www.retailer-savings.com/contact2.cgi?config=9597).<br>    * The following link for requests to opt out: [Do Not Sell My Personal Information](https://www.retailer-savings.com/contact2.cgi?config=9597).<br>    <br>    **Verification Process and Required Information.** Note that we may need to request additional information from you to verify your identity or understand the scope of your request, although you will not be required to create an account with us to submit a request or have it fulfilled. We will require you to provide, at a minimum, your email address used at the time of signup and any additional data points including but not limited to first name, last name, physical address, date of birth, phone number, and an affidavit to prove your identity.<br>    <br>    **Authorized Agent** You may designate an authorized agent to make a CCPA request on your behalf by:<br>    <br>    * Providing the authorized agent with written permission to submit CCPA requests on your behalf and verifying your identity directly with us; or<br>    * Providing the authorized agent with power of attorney.<br>    <br>    We may require the authorized agent to submit a copy of the power of attorney form or the written permission form you provided to the agent to us. We may ask for copies of such forms in order to prove that the agent has been authorized by you to submit CCPA requests on your behalf.<br>    <br>    **Minors' Right to Opt In.** We do not sell the personal information of minors under 18 years of age.<br>    <br>    **Contact for More Information.** For questions or concerns about USA Interactive, Inc.'s privacy policy or practices, please [click here](https://www.retailer-savings.com/contact.cgi?config=9597) to contact us, call us at (866) 436-7542, or write to us at 2207 Concord Pike PMB 530, Wilmington, DE 19803.<br>    <br>    **HOW DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION AND WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**<br>    <br>    We collect and combine personally identifiable information (“PII”) and non-personally identifiable information (“Non-PII”) through various sources, including those discussed below. For your reference, PII is data collected with an intention to specifically identify, contact or locate a person, including but not limited to name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. Conversely, Non-PII is data that is not used to specifically identify, contact or locate an individual, including but not limited to zip code, gender, age, or IP address.<br>    <br>    **Website Registration Forms**<br>    <br>    We collect information about you when you register on one of our websites. This registration information may include, but is not limited to your:<br>    <br>    * e-mail address<br>    * full name<br>    * mailing address<br>    * telephone number<br>    * date of birth<br>    * gender<br>    <br>    **Offer Forms**<br>    <br>    We also collect information about you when you complete a survey or offer form on one of our websites or web pages. This information may include, but is not limited to: your e-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, and payment information; information about your background, interests, health, education, career goals, and shopping preferences; and any other personal information or unique preference information you provide to us or our advertisers.<br>    <br>    **Distribution Partners**<br>    <br>    Website operators that license our ad serving technology pass information to us so that we may serve advertisements to you. The information passed may include, but is not limited to, your IP address, e-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, date of birth, and gender.<br>    <br>    **Publisher Partners**<br>    <br>    When you complete a registration or offer form that is hosted by one of our website publisher partners on our behalf, the website publisher partner may submit all or a portion of the information that you submitted on the form to the Company. This information may include, but is not limited to: your IP address, e-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, and payment information; information about your background, interests, health, education, career goals, and shopping preferences; and any other information you provide to our website publisher partner.<br>    <br>    **Marketing Partners**<br>    <br>    We may receive information about you, including but not limited to your IP address, e-mail address, first name, last name, mailing address, and telephone number, from third party marketing partners that provide us with consumer data to manage on their behalf.<br>    <br>    **Automatic Information/Digital Identifiers**<br>    <br>    We may automatically receive and store certain types of information about you through the data sources listed above.<br>    <br>    You may be familiar with the term “cookies,” which are unique alphanumeric identifiers that store information on your computer. A cookie is placed on your computer when your web browser accesses our website. We use cookies for tracking transactions and the user characteristics explained in detail throughout this Privacy Policy. If you choose, there are utilities available for purchase from independent software providers to install on your computer as well as tools/preferences you can choose through most web browsers to make website visits anonymous. Of course, cookies let you have a more satisfying website experience, so we recommend that you leave them turned on.<br>    <br>    We may also add third party cookies. Cookies contain anonymous, segmented data about a user’s demographics (like age, gender, and location), interests, lifestyle, household details, social media memberships, and online influences. The data in the cookies may also contain individual-specific information relating to web browsing and app activity.<br>    <br>    We also collect information through our web server applications. This information includes your Internet Protocol or “IP” address, date/time stamp, browser type, and referring URL.<br>    <br>    Additionally, we may use pixel tracking technology to track the completion of transactions with us or our advertisers, the source information for those transactions, and your IP address, date/time stamp, browser type, and referring URL.<br>    <br>    **Government Forms**<br>    <br>    The Company may be required to create, collect, maintain, and submit certain information required by the government, such as IRS Forms W-9 and 1099. This information, which may include your taxpayer identification number, will not be used, shared, transferred, or sold for marketing purposes.<br>    <br>    **HOW DO WE USE THIS INFORMATION?**<br>    <br>    We may use the collected PII and Non-PII for any legally permissible purpose in our sole discretion, including but not limited to those explained below.<br>    <br>    **Ad Serving**<br>    <br>    We may serve advertisements to you based, in part, on your IP address, the demographic and geographic information you submitted to the Company during the website registration process, and other socio-economic information, psychographic information, Internet behavior (i.e., browsing, search, shopping, purchase, and ad response behavior), and lifestyle information about you that we obtain from other Company entities and from third parties.<br>    <br>    We also use third party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our websites. These companies may use and optimize information (not including your name, mailing address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.<br>    <br>    **Pre-select/Pre-fill Offers**<br>    <br>    Our website technology may pre-select certain offers for you to view based on the demographic and geographic information you submitted to the Company during the website registration process. Additionally, this technology may pre-fill some or all of the offers’ data fields with the information you submitted during the website registration process in order to prevent you from having to re-enter this information. We may not show all of the pre-filled data fields to you.<br>    <br>    **Upsell**<br>    <br>    We utilize customized post transactional or "upsell" technology to help advertisers generate sales, while providing you with a series of great offers we think may be of interest to you. The way it works is simple: once you purchase a product or service from one of our reward advertisers, you will be offered additional products or services that we think may be of interest to you. If you elect to purchase products or services from a third party advertiser in the post transactional channel, please input all necessary information on the subsequent advertiser form, including, but not limited to, your credit card information. You need to complete this information because we do not pass this information to the third party advertiser.<br>    <br>    **Customer Service and Fulfillment**<br>    <br>    We may use your information to operate the website promotion, service your account and to fulfill rewards earned through Company websites. We may also use your information to verify your identity or claimed account status and, where we consider appropriate, investigate your compliance with the terms and conditions of the website promotion or any advertiser offer. We do retain customer service correspondence.<br>    <br>    **Credit Card Preauthorization**<br>    <br>    By submitting your credit card information to us or to one of our advertisers, you are authorizing the Company or its agent to periodically verify that your credit card account is valid and has credit available by charging, and thereafter crediting, a small sum to the card.<br>    <br>    **Marketing**<br>    <br>    We may use your information in our online (e.g., e-mail marketing) and offline (e.g., telemarketing, cell phone text messaging, skip tracing, and direct mail) marketing programs. With respect to telemarketing in particular, you authorize us and our third-party marketing partners to call your landline telephone and/or cell phone (if provided) by providing "prior express consent". You understand that your wireless carrier's standard rates may apply to any calls to your cell phone. If you would like to be removed from these programs, [click here](#) and follow the opt-out instructions.<br>    <br>    **SMS**<br>    <br>    SMS, Wireless and Other Mobile Offerings: Some of the services that we provide will result in sending an SMS, wireless or other mobile offering to your cell phone. These should be obvious in the context of the offering at the time you sign up. By signing up, you are agreeing to receive these mobile offerings. You understand that your wireless carrier's standard rates apply to these messages. To unsubscribe or discontinue SMS messages, send "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received. This process impacts only the future delivery of the particular SMS message offering, so you must send that message for each offering. This will not affect offerings sent on behalf of third parties.<br>    <br>    **IVR**<br>    <br>    Your acceptance of the terms and conditions of this website constitutes your express written consent to receive telemarketing calls from third-party marketers, including by means of a pre-recorded message and automated voice dialing. Your consent will be effective regardless of whether the number you have provided: (a) is a home, business, or cell phone line; and/or (b) is or will be registered on any state or federal Do-Not-Call (DNC) list, and shall remain in effect until you revoke your consent by contacting us.<br>    <br>    **HOW DO WE SHARE INFORMATION?**<br>    <br>    We may share the collected PII and Non-PII for any legally permissible purpose in our sole discretion, including but not limited to those explained below.<br>    <br>    **Within the Company**<br>    <br>    We may share information we collect with affiliated companies, including our parent company and other subsidiaries of our parent company, for use in their ad serving and marketing programs. This Privacy Policy does not apply to affiliated companies and their collection, use and sharing of information. With respect to online behavioral advertising, certain affiliated companies may use non-personally identifiable information (which may or may not include click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) collected during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).<br>    <br>    **Vendors**<br>    <br>    We may share your information with various third party vendors that are not part of the Company, including but not limited to vendors that provide us with technology to deploy commercial e-mail, vendors that sell the products or services for which you have qualified through one of our websites, and shipping companies that we utilize to ship products to you.<br>    <br>    **Advertisers**<br>    <br>    When you participate in an offer by completing a form, we will transfer the information you submitted on the form to the applicable advertiser.<br>    <br>    When you answer “yes” or “no” to a survey question, some or all of the information that you submitted during the website registration process will be transferred to advertisers that we believe may be of interest to you without providing you with another opportunity to review the information.<br>    <br>    If you sign up for email job alerts, we will send you job alerts via email. You can unsubscribe from these job alerts at any time. We will share your email address and job-related preferences with the vendor that we use to send you email job alerts.<br>    <br>    When you select “yes” next to an offer, we will transfer some or all of the information that you submitted during the website registration process to the applicable advertiser without providing you with another opportunity to review the information.<br>    <br>    **Ad Serving Companies**<br>    <br>    We may use third party ad networks or ad serving companies to serve advertisements on our websites. We pass information about you to these companies so that they can deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of interest to you. The information passed to these companies may include, but is not limited to, your IP address, e-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, and any other information you provide to us. Web pages that are served by these companies will state that they are “powered by” or “ads by” the applicable company and will contain a link to that company’s privacy policy.<br>    <br>    **Marketing Partners**<br>    <br>    We may share, license or sell your information to third parties for various marketing purposes, including their online (e.g., e-mail marketing) and offline (e.g., telemarketing, cell phone text messaging, skip tracing, and direct mail) marketing programs. With respect to telemarketing in particular, you authorize us and our third-party marketing partners to call your landline telephone and/or cell phone (if provided) by providing "prior express consent" and you understand that your wireless carrier's standard rates may apply to any calls to your cell phone.<br>    <br>    **Data Enhancement/Appending/Validation**<br>    <br>    We may use third party service providers to enhance our database with additional elements, including but not limited to age ranges present in your household, whether you own or rent a home, the length of time you have lived at your residence, whether you are a mail order buyer or responder, household income, and gender. Further, we may use third party service providers to append telephone numbers to other data points we have in our database. We also may use third party service providers to validate the data we have in our database.<br>    <br>    Additionally, we may share, license or sell your information to third parties for use in their data validation, enhancement, information verification services, and, to the extent permitted by law, individual reference or look-up services. These third parties use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes.<br>    <br>    **Governmental Agencies or Other Companies**<br>    <br>    We may share your information with law enforcement officials or governmental agencies: (1) in response to their request; (2) when permitted or required by law; or (3) to establish our compliance with applicable laws, rules, regulations, or guidelines.<br>    <br>    We may store and share your information with third parties for suppression or opt-out purposes.<br>    <br>    We also may share your information with third parties when: (1) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; (2) investigating fraud that has already taken place; (3) enforcing or applying existing terms and conditions and/or other agreements; (4) protecting the rights, property or safety of our websites, our users or others; or (5) responding to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.<br>    <br>    In all cases, this information is not provided to these entities or persons for marketing purposes.<br>    <br>    **Right to Transfer**<br>    <br>    Should the Company choose to sell or transfer business assets, it is possible that the information we possess may be transferred as part of that transaction. The Company may decide to retain a copy of the information post sale or transfer.<br>    <br>    **COMPANY CUSTOMER CHOICES**<br>    <br>    **Marketing Communications**<br>    <br>    By completing and submitting a Company registration form, you are consenting to receive marketing communications from the Company and its third party marketing partners, including Lumber Road Media, LLC. If, after you have shared your information with the Company, you decide that you do not want to receive marketing communications from the Company and its third party marketing partners, you can discontinue the communications by [clicking here](#) and following the opt-out instructions. If you have registered or submitted information under more than one e-mail account, you must submit separate unsubscribe requests for each account.<br>    <br>    **Request for More Information**<br>    <br>    As it relates to marketing communications or any other questions you might have about our Privacy Policy, [click here to contact us](#) or write to us at 2207 Concord Pike PMB 530, Wilmington, DE 19803.<br>    <br>    **Opt-Out of Third Party Cookies**<br>    <br>    In visiting this site, a third-party advertiser (or its partners) may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. These cookies enable more customized ads, content or services to be provided to you. To trigger these cookies, we may pass an encrypted or “hashed” (non-human readable) identifier corresponding to your email address to a Web advertising partner, who may place a cookie on your computer. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to, these cookies. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) or [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).<br>    <br>    Our partners use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms, including but not limited to, computers and mobile devices, over time for advertising (including addressable TV), analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. Your data may be transferred outside of the country from which it was originally collected. To learn more about interest-based advertising in general and to opt-out, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). To opt-out of the use of your mobile device ID for targeted advertising, please see [http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices](hhttp://www.aboutads.info/appchoices).<br>    <br>    Our third-party cookie partners include LiveRamp (for LiveRamp's opt-out requests, please visit [https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)), Traverse (for Traverse's privacy policy, please visit [http://www.traversedlp.com/privacy](http://www.traversedlp.com/privacy)), and others.<br>    <br>    **WHAT HAPPENS IF I HIT A LINK TO ANOTHER SITE FROM A COMPANY WEBSITE?**<br>    <br>    Our websites may offer links to other websites. Other websites have their own terms of use and privacy and security policies. If you choose to visit one of these sites, you should review the policies that govern that particular site.<br>    <br>    **APPLICATION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**<br>    <br>    This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected by or submitted to the Company. Other affiliated entities of the Company may obtain information independently from transactions and experiences with you or from other sources. This Privacy Policy does not pertain to that information.<br>    <br>    **WHAT IS THE POLICY WITH RESPECT TO COMMUNICATING WITH CHILDREN?**<br>    <br>    We recognize the unique privacy concerns regarding children. We are committed to carefully protecting privacy where children are involved no matter the point of contact. In particular, our intention is to fully comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). Per COPPA guidelines, we do not knowingly collect PII from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian is made aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with PII through any point of contact, [click here to contact us](#) and we will delete the information about the child referenced from our files.<br>    <br>    **SECURITY**<br>    <br>    There is no such thing as complete security on the Internet or otherwise. The Company uses various security techniques on our websites to help protect against the loss, misuse or modification of information we’ve collected from you. When you access your personal information or transmit information to us, that information is stored on servers that we have taken steps to protect from unauthorized access or intrusion. While we strive to protect your information, the Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with the Company, its partners and affiliates.<br>    <br>    **LIMITATION OF LIABILITY**<br>    <br>    YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS WELL AS THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS WEBSITE (INCLUDING LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES). YOU AGREE THAT THE COMPANY’S LIABILITY FOR ANY BREACH OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE VALUE OF THE TRANSACTIONS OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY THE COMPANY TO THE EXTENT SUCH CLAIM IS NOT OTHERWISE BARRED BY OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS. |     |
| Copyright © 2024 Retailer-Savings.com. All Rights Reserved. | [CLOSE](javascript:window.close();) |
